LEISURE TIME WITH PROPHET T.B. JOSHUA
Leisure Time With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Playing with nature is a leisure time with nature to ease tension and stress.
I want to encourage you to often find a natural environment to read your Bible
because a natural environment is natural and free from distraction.
Nature itself enhances spirituality.
I often read my Bible in a calm and quiet environment
because the Bible is not like other books you can read anywhere and understand.
Understanding of the Bible is understanding the nature of God.
Leisure Time With Prophet T.B. Joshua
It must be read in an enabling environment to understand it.
To live it, it must be read in an enabling environment.
To teach it, it can be read anywhere.
Leisure Time With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Leisure time - time to be refreshed and be renewed.
God's Word refreshes our mind.
God's Spirit renews our strength.
Leisure Time With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Prophet T.B. Joshua Weaving Native Baskets
Prophet T.B. Joshua Joins The Youth In A Game Of Football
TT: Mel Flowers 02/08/2018
RV: ROBERT BEGIER 11/08/2018